webhr.co 2019-12-09

# Privacy Policy of WebHR

**Last Updated: January 01, 2019**

WebHR is a Cloud based HR Software developed by Verge Inc. We at WebHR understand that your privacy is very important. To better protect your privacy, we are always committed to giving you transparency of our privacy practices and our control over your data in connection with WebHR's Services, in complete confidence the data collected through the WebHR is intended to be restricted to the purposes of delivering services for which the User or Client has utilized (as defined in our Terms of Service). 

This privacy policy applies to all data from visitors, clients (collectively "Users", "You"), Verge Inc. suite of software and applications includes but not limited to, online services, mobile services, integrations and all other services that Verge Inc. fulfills (collectively, the "Services") 

WebHR may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make material changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Service or sending you an email. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when they use the Service after such changes have been first posted.

### What information does WebHR collect ?

WebHR receives and stores personal and company information you enter on our Service. The types of Personal Information collected are as follows:

  * PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION - First and Last name, Addresses, Telephone numbers, Social Security number, Birthdays and anything that pertains to the user as to identify for HR purposes.

  * PERSONAL ONLINE CREDENTIALS - Email addresses, Usernames, Passwords, Security questions, Account tokens to properly secure the client's account and the whole service itself.

  * GEOLOCATION DATA - Current location address and location coordinates (longitude and latitude), to allow location-based features and services to properly work like e-Track and geofencing.

  * BANK INFORMATION - Account Numbers and Routing numbers to process payments, invoices, and provide payroll services.

  * COOKIES - Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive. Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

### Is my company information secure ?

WebHR has implemented World Class Security standards to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Access to your data through your WebHR account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. We have also implemented an SSL Encryption and paired it with HTTPS technology to provide top notch security and secure transmission over the cloud to and from your browser. These technologies add an extra layer of security by wrapping your data through a secure shell when transmitting to the cloud. You also need to prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

### What is my control over my data ?

As clients and users of WebHR you are classified as Data Subjects (collectively "Users", "You") are the owner of these data; Verge Inc. (collectively, the "Services") and its affiliates as Data Processor and Data Controllers, responsibility to grant Data Subjects have a right to access, to modify, correct, or delete personal information controlled by Verge Inc. and its affiliates as necessary.

WebHR will withhold the personal information you provide while your account is in existence or as needed to provide you the Service. We may withhold Customer or User information if retention is reasonably necessary to comply with our legal obligations, meet regulatory requirements, resolve disputes between Customer, Users, or related parties, prevent fraud and abuse, or enforce this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use Agreement. In response to lawful requirements WebHR will withhold data to disclose personal information to lawful requests by public authorities, including but not limited to meet national security, law enforcement requirements or any lawful proceedings regarding these data. 

If you terminate your account, your complete company information, will be removed from the site and deleted from our servers. Should you ever decide to delete your WebHR account, you may do so by sending us a request at [support@webhr.co](mailto:support@webhr.co?Subject=Delete%20Data).

### What If I Have Questions Or Concerns ?

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy using WebHR, please send a detailed message to: [info@webhr.co](mailto:support@webhr.co?Subject=Privacy%20Policy) We will try our best to resolve your concerns at our earliest.

### What is relationship between Verge Inc. and WebHR ?

Verge Inc. is the Parent Company that fully owns WebHR as one of its core products. For more information about Verge please visit our website at [http://verge.co](http://verge.co/).

### Do we comply with EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework ?

WebHR complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. Verge Inc. (on behalf of WebHR) has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/> WebHR's participation in the Privacy Shield applies to all Personal Information that is subject to this privacy policy and is received from individuals who are resident in the European Union, European Economic Area. WebHR will comply with the Privacy Shield Principles in respect of such Personal Information. WebHR's accountability for Personal Information that it receives under the Privacy Shield and subsequently transfers to a third party is described in the Privacy Shield Principles located at https://www.privacyshield.gov/EU-US-Framework. In particular, WebHR remains responsible and liable under the Privacy Shield Principles if third-party agents that it engages to process the personal data on its behalf do so in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless WebHR proves that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage. For human resources data of EU residents we have agreed to cooperate with local Data Protection Authorities. WebHR has chosen to cooperate with EU Data Protection Authorities (DPAs) and comply with the information and advice provided to it by an informal panel of DPAs in relation to such unresolved complaints (as further described in the Privacy Shield Principles). Please contact us to be directed to the relevant DPA contacts. As further explained in the Privacy Shield Principles, a binding arbitration option will also be made available to you in order to address residual complaints not resolved by any other means. WebHR is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC). In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, WebHR commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact WebHR at: [support@webhr.co](mailto:support@webhr.co?Subject=Privacy%20Policy) WebHR has further committed to cooperate with the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) with regard to unresolved Privacy Shield complaints concerning data transferred from the EU. 

### Data collected on WebHR

WebHR does not have any any direct or indirect relationship with the individuals personal data that is processed by the software or that is stored in the database.

If you are an Employee of one of the Clients that use WebHR as its Cloud based HR Software provider, and if you would no longer like to be involved with the Client, then contact the Client directly regarding this concern.

WebHR may transfer Personal Information to companies that provide services to us. These transfer are covered by the provisions in this Privacy Policy regarding notice and choice and the service agreements with our Clients.

WebHR has no direct or indirect relationship with the individuals whose personal data is either processed within the system, or is stored in one of the databases.

Any individual that wants access to the data (whether to amend / correct or delete any set of data) must contact the Client directly. The Client can update or remove data without WebHR's involvement. If the Client requests WebHR to remove any data, we will respond to the request within 07 days.

WebHR will retain Personal Information for all employees of a Client for as long as the Client is Active. When a Client deactivates their services with WebHR, we will retain their information for a specific time frame as necessary to comply with our legal requirements.

### For further questions

For questions related to this Privacy Policy, please contact us: 

Verge Inc.  
44240 Fremont Blvd, Fremont, CA, 94538, USA  
Phone: +1-801-901-0090  
Email: [support@webhr.co](mailto:support@webhr.co?Subject=Privacy%20Policy)
